Salem Witchcraft Papers from the Essex County Court Archives
University of Virginia Library
Salem Witchcraft Papers from the Essex County Court Archives
Introduction
The SALEM WITCHCRAFT PAPERS at the Essex Institute contain two separate collections: The Essex County Court Archives and the Essex Institute Collection. The Essex County Archives Collection, under the jurisdiction of the Supreme Judicial Court, was deposited at the Essex Institute by the Supreme Court in December, 1980. The Essex Institute Collection is comprised of witchcraft documents found in several of the Institute's collections of family papers.
Both collections contain legal documents of the Salem Witchcraft Trials of 1692. They have been indexed by name for both plaintiffs and defendants. Transcriptions of these documents, as well as additional witchcraft documents held in other archives, were published in Paul Boyer and Stephen Nissenbaum's The Salem Witchcraft Papers (New York, DaCapo Press, 1971).
- Volume 1
  - Warrant for Jurors for the Court of Oyer and Terminer, ecca1001
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 1.
  - Oaths of Thomas Newton as Attorney General and Stephen Sewall as Clerk of the Court of Oyer and Terminer, ecca1002
    ECCA, vol. 1, no. 2.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Sarah Good for Afflicting Sarah Bibber, ecca1003
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 3.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Good, ecca1004
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 4.
  - Indictment No. 3 of Sarah Good for Afflicting Ann Putnam Jr., ecca1005
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 5.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Sarah Good, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1006
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 6.
  - Witnesses v. Sarah Good, ecca1007
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 7.
  - Mittimus for Sarah Good & Tituba, ecca1008
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 8.
  - Examinations of Sarah Good, Sarah Osburn & Tituba, as Recorded by Joseph Putnam, ecca1009
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 9.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Sarah Good, ecca1010
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 10.
  - Examinations of Sarah Good, Sarah Osburn & Tituba, as Recorded by Ezekiel Cheever, ecca1011
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 11 & 12.
  - Summary of Evidence v. Sarah Good, ecca1013
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 13.
  - Examinations & Mittimus of Sarah Good, Sarah Osburn, & Tituba, as Recorded by John Hathorne, ecca1014
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 14.
  - Depositions of Sarah & Thomas Gadge v. Sarah Good, ecca1015
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 15.
  - Deposition of Joseph Herrick Sr. & Mary Herrick v. Sarah Good, ecca1016
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 16.
  - Testimony of William Batten, William Shaw & Deborah Shaw v. Sarah Good, ecca1017
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 17.
  - Deposition of Samuel Abbey & Mary Abbey v. Sarah Good, ecca1018
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 18.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Sarah Good, ecca1019
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 19.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Sarah Good, ecca1020
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 20.
  - Deposition of Henry Herrick & Jonathan Batchelor v. Sarah Good, ecca1021
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 21.
  - Deposition of Johanna Childen v. Sarah Good, ecca1022
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 22.
  - Deposition of Susannah Shelden v. Sarah Good, ecca1023
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 23.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Sarah Good, ecca1024
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 24.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. Sarah Good, ecca1025
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 25.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. Sarah Good, ecca1026
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 26.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Sarah Osburn, ecca1027
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 27.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Sarah Osburn, ecca1028
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 28.
  - Statement of William Allen, John Hughes, William Good, & Samuel Braybrook v. Sarah Good, Sarah Osburn, & Tituba, ecca1029
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 29.
  - Testimony of Mercy Lewis v. Sarah Osburn, ecca1030
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 30.
  - Testimony of Abigail Williams v. Sarah Good, Sarah Osburn, & Tituba, ecca1031
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 31.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Tituba, ecca1032
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 32.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Osburn & Tituba, and Officer's Return, ecca1033
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 33.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris, Thomas Putnam, & Ezekiel Cheever v. Sarah Good, Sarah Osburn, & Tituba, ecca1034
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 34.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Tituba, ecca1035
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 35.
  - Mittimus for Martha Cory, Rebecca Nurse, Dorothy Good, Sarah Cloyce, John Procter, & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1036
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 36.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Martha Cory, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1037
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 37.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Martha Cory, ecca1038
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 38.
  - Deposition of Ezekiel Cheever & Edward Putnam v. Martha Cory, ecca1039
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 39.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Martha Cory, Mary Esty, Sarah Cloyce, & Giles Cory, ecca1040
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 40.
  - Deposition of Ephraim Shelden v. Sarah Cloyce, ecca1041
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 41.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris, Nathaniel Ingersoll, & Thomas Putnam v. Martha Cory, ecca1042
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 42.
  - Statement of Giles Cory Concerning Martha Cory, ecca1043
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 43.
  - Indictment No. 3 of John Procter, for Afflicting Mary Warren, ecca1044
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 44.
  - Indictment No. 2 of John Procter, for Affllicting Mercy Lewis, ecca1045
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 45.
  - Indictment No. 1 of John Procter, for Afflicting Mary Walcott (Returned Ignoramus), ecca1046
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 46.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris, Nathaniel Ingersoll, & Thomas Putnam v. John Procter, Elizabeth Procter, & Sarah Cloyce, ecca1047
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 47.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam & John Putnam Jr. v. John Procter, ecca1048
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 48.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. John Procter, ecca1049
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 49.
  - Physical Examinations of the Bodies of John Procter & John Willard, ecca1050
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 50.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth v. John Procter, ecca1051
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 51.
  - Samuel Parris's Record of Samuel Sibley v. John Procter, ecca1052
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 52.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. John Procter, Elizabeth Procter & Sarah Cloyce, ecca1053
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 53.
  - Testimony of Abigail Williams v. John Procter, ecca1054
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 54.
  - Statement of Mary Warren v. John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1055
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 55.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. John Procter, ecca1056
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 56.
  - Statement of Samuel Parris Concerning Abigail Williams & Mary Walcott v. John Procter, Elizabeth Procter, Sarah Cloyce, Martha Cory, Rebecca Nurse, Sarah Good & Dorothy Good, ecca1057
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 57.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott & Elizabeth Hubbard v. John Procter, Elizabeth Procter, Benjamin Procter, & Sarah Procter; Testimony of James Holton v. John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1058
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 58.
  - Deposition of Mary Warren v. John Procter, ecca1059
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 59.
  - Petition in Support of John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1060
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 60.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Dorothy Good, and Officer's Return, ecca1061
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 61.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. Dorothy Good, ecca1062
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 62.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Dorothy Good, ecca1063
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 63.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Dorothy Good, ecca1064
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 64.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1065
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 65.
  - Indictment No. 3 of Rebecca Nurse, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1066
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 66.
  - Indictment No. 4 of Rebecca Nurse, for Afflicting Abigail Williams, ecca1067
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 67.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Rebecca Nurse, for Afflicting Mary Walcott, ecca1068
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 68.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Rebecca Nurse, for Afflicting Ann Putnam Jr., ecca1069
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 69.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Rebecca Nurse, ecca1070
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 70.
  - Warrant for the Execution of Bridget Bishop, ecca1071
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 71.
  - Examination of Rebecca Nurse, ecca1072
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 72.
  - Testimony of Abigail Williams v. Rebecca Nurse & Sarah Cloyce, ecca1073
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 73.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1074
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 74.
  - Deposition of Edward Putnam v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1075
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 75.
  - Deposition of Johanna Childen v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1076
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 76.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris & John Putnam Sr. v. Rebecca Nurse & Martha Carrier, ecca1077
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 77.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1078
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 78.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris, Nathaniel Ingersoll & Thomas Putnam v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1079
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 79.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1080
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 80.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1081
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 81.
  - Deposition of John Putnam Jr. & Hannah Putnam v. Rebecca Nurse, Mary Esty, & Sarah Cloyce, ecca1082
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 82.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Sr., v. Rebecca Nurse, Sarah Cloyce, Sarah Bishop, & Elizabeth Cary, ecca1083
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 83.
  - Deposition of Sarah Holten v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1084
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 84.
  - Testimony of Rebecca Preston & Mary Tarbell for Rebecca Nurse, ecca1085
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 85.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam & Edward Putnam v. Rebecca Nurse, ecca1086
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 86.
  - Statement of Samuel Nurse & John Tarbell for Rebecca Nurse, ecca1087
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 87.
  - Petition of Rebecca Nurse, ecca1088
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 88.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Elizabeth Procter, for Afflicting Mercy Lewis, ecca1089
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 89.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Elizabeth Procter, for Afflicting Mary Walcott, ecca1090
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 90.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Cloyce & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1091
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 91.
  - Council Record Pertaining to Sarah Cloyce, Martha Cory, Dorothy Good, Rebecca Nurse, Elizabeth Procter, & John Procter, ecca1092
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 92.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam & Edward Putnam v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1093
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 93.
  - Testimony of Abigail Williams v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1094
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 94.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1095
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 95.
  - Complaint of Jonathan Walcott & Nathaniel Ingersoll v. Sarah Cloyce & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1096
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 96.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1097
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 97.
  - Testimony of William Rayment Regarding Some of the Afflicted Persons, in Support of Elizabeth Procter, Copy, ecca1098
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 98.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1099
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 99.
  - Deposition of Stephen Bittford v. Elizabeth Procter & Rebecca Nurse, ecca1100
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 100.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr. v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1101
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 101.
  - Deposition of Mary Warren v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1102
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 102.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1103
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 103.
  - Testimony of Elizabeth Booth v. John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1104
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 104 & Vol. 2 no. 112.
  - Testimony of Elizabeth Booth v. Elizabeth Procter & John Willard, ecca1105
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 105.
  - Deposition of Joseph Bayley & Wife v. Elizabeth Procter, ecca1106
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 106.
  - Testimony of Samuel Barton for Elizabeth Procter; Testimony of John Houghton for Elizabeth Procter, ecca1107
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 107.
  - Declaration of Arthur Abbot Concerning Testimony About Elizabeth Procter, ecca1108
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 108.
  - Testimony of Daniel Elliot for Elizabeth Procter, ecca1109
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 109.
  - Petition in Support of John Procter & Elizabeth Procter, ecca1110
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 110.
  - Examination of Mary Warren, ecca1111
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 111.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Giles Cory, Mary Warren, Abigail Hobbs, & Bridget Bishop, with Summons for Witnesses v. Giles Cory et al., ecca1112
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 112.
  - Examination of Mary Warren, ecca1113
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 113 & 114.
  - Examination of Mary Warren in Prison, ecca1115
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 115.
  - Examination of Mary Warren, ecca1116
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 116.
  - Statement of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Mary Warren, ecca1117
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 117 & 152 MSJC, JA, on deposit at the Phillips Library. PEM, Salem, MA.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth v. Daniel Andrew & Mary Warren, ecca1118
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 118.
  - Testimony of Mary English Regarding Mary Warren, ecca1119
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 119.
  - Testimony of Edward Bishop, Sarah Bishop & Mary Esty Regarding Mary Warren, ecca1120
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 120.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Bridget Bishop, for Afflicting Mercy Lewis, ecca1121
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 121.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Bridget Bishop, for Afflicting Abigail Williams, ecca1122
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 122.
  - Indictment No. 4 of Bridget Bishop, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1123
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 123.
  - Indictment No. 5 of Bridget Bishop, for Afflicting Ann Putnam Jr., ecca1124
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 124.
  - Examination of Bridget Bishop, as Recorded by Samuel Parris, ecca1125
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 125.
  - Physical Examinations No. 1 & No. 2 of Bridget Bishop, Rebecca Nurse, Elizabeth Procter, Alice Parker, Susannah Martin, & Sarah Good, ecca1136
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 136.
  - Examination of Bridget Bishop, as Recorded by Ezekiel Cheever, ecca1137
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 137.
  - Deposition of William Stacy v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1138
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 138 & 139.
  - Examination of Deliverance Hobbs in Prison, ecca1140
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 140.
  - Testimony of Samuel Gray v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1141
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 141.
  - Deposition of Rev. John Hale v. Sarah Bishop, ecca1142
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 142.
  - Deposition of Samuel & Sarah Shattuck v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1144
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 144.
  - Testimony of John Louder v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1145
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 145.
  - Testimony of Richard Coman v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1146
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 146.
  - Testimony of John Bly Sr. & William Bly v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1147
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 147.
  - Testimony of John Cook v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1148
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 148.
  - Deposition of Susannah Shelden v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1149
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 149.
  - Testimony of John Bly Sr., & Rebecca Bly v. Bridget Bishop, ecca1150
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 150.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Balch & Abigail Waldon v. Sarah Bishop, ecca1151
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 151.
  - Examinations of Abigail Hobbs in Prison, ecca1155
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 155.
  - Examination of Abigail Hobbs, ecca1156
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 156.
  - Testimony of Lydia Nichols & Elizabeth Nichols v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1157
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 157.
  - Deposition of Margaret Knight v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1158
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 158.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1159
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 159.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1160
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 160.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1161
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 161.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Abigail Hobbs, ecca1162
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 162.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Sarah Wilds, William Hobbs, Deliverance Hobbs, Nehemiah Abbott Jr., Mary Esty, Edward Bishop Jr., Sarah Bishop, Mary Black, & Mary English., ecca1163
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 163.
  - Examinations of Sarah Wilds & William Hobbs, ecca1164
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 164.
  - Ephraim Wilds for Sarah Wilds, ecca1165
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 165.
  - Testimony of John Wilds & Ephraim Wilds for Sarah Wilds, ecca1166
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 166.
  - Names of Some Witnesses v. Sarah Wilds & Notation Concerning Sarah Good, ecca1167
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 167.
  - Statement of Susannah Shelden v. Philip English, Sarah Buckley, Mary Whittredge, Bridget Bishop, Mary English, Giles & Martha Cory, ecca1168
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 168, 153 & 154.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Philip English, Sarah Morey & Dorcas Hoar, ecca1169
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 169.
  - Warrant No. 2 for the Apprehension of Philip English, ecca1170
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 170.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Susannah Martin, ecca1171
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 171.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Susannah Martin, for Afflicting Mercy Lewis, ecca1172
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 172.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Susannah Martin, for Afflicting Mary Walcott, ecca1173
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 173.
  - Examination of Susannah Martin, ecca1174
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 174.
  - Examination of Susannah Martin, Revised Version, ecca1175
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 175.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. Susannah Martin, ecca1176
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 176.
  - Mittimus for Susannah Martin, Lydia Dustin, Dorcas Hoar & Sarah Morey, ecca1177
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 177.
  - Testimony of Abigail Williams v. Susannah Martin, ecca1178
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 178.
  - Deposition of William Brown v. Susannah Martin, ecca1179
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 179 & 180.
  - Deposition of Jarvis Ring v. Susannah Martin and Deposition of Joseph Ring v. Susannah Martin & Thomas Hardy, ecca1181
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 181 & 185.
  - Testimony and Deposition of John Pressey v. Susannah Martin, ecca1182
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 182.
  - Deposition of John Pressey & Mary Pressey v. Susannah Martin, ecca1183
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 183.
  - Deposition of Bernard Peach v. Susannah Martin, ecca1184
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 184.
  - ecca1185
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 185.
  - Deposition of John Kimball v. Susannah Martin, ecca1186
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 186.
  - Deposition of John Kimball v. Susannah Martin, ecca1187
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 187.
  - Deposition of John Allen v. Susannah Martin, ecca1188
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 188.
  - Deposition of Bernard Peach v. Susannah Martin, ecca1189
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 189.
  - Deposition of Joseph Knight & Elizabeth Clark v. Susannah Martin, ecca1190
    ECCA, Vol. 1, nos. 190 & 192.
  - Depositions of Robert Downer, Mary Andrews, & Moses Pike v. Susannah Martin, ecca1191
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 191.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam v. Susannah Martin; Testimony of Nathaniel Ingersoll v. Susannah Martin, ecca1193
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 193.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris, Nathaniel Ingersoll & Thomas Putnam v. Susannah Martin, ecca1194
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 194.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. Susannah Martin, ecca1195
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 195.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Susannah Martin, ecca1196
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 196.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. Susannah Martin, ecca1197
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 197.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Susannah Martin, ecca1198
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 198.
  - Testimony of John Atkinson v. Susannah Martin, ecca1199
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 199.
  - Testimony of Sarah Atkinson v. Susannah Martin, ecca1200
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 200.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of Elizabeth Hart & Thomas Farrar Sr., ecca1201
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 201.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Elizabeth Hart, ecca1203
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 203.
  - Indictment No. 2 of Dorcas Hoar, for Afflicting Mary Walcott, ecca1204
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 204.
  - Indictment No. 1 of Dorcas Hoar, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1205
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 205.
  - Examination of Dorcas Hoar, ecca1206
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 206.
  - Deposition of Hannah Cox & Rachel Tuck v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1207
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 207.
  - Deposition of John Richards & Joseph Morgan v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1208
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 208.
  - Deposition of Sarah Bibber v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1209
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 209.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1210
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 210.
  - Testimony of John Hale v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1211
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 211.
  - Deposition of Mary Walcott v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1212
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 212.
  - Deposition of Ann Putnam Jr., v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1213
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 213.
  - Depositions of Joseph & Deborah Morgan v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1214
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 214.
  - Deposition of Edward Hooper v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1215
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 215.
  - Deposition of John Tuck & Joseph Tuck v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1216
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 216.
  - Deposition of Maria Gage v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1217
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 217.
  - Deposition of Thomas Putnam & Edward Putnam v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1218
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 218.
  - Deposition of John Lovet v. Dorcas Hoar, ecca1219
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 219.
  - Warrant for the Apprehension of George Jacobs Sr. & Margaret Jacobs, ecca1220
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 220.
  - Complaint of Nathaniel Ingersoll & Thomas Putnam v. George Jacobs Jr., Daniel Andrew, Rebecca Jacobs, Sarah Buckley, Mary Whittredge, Elizabeth Hart, Thomas Farrer Sr., Elizabeth Colson, & Bethia Carter Jr., ecca1221
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 221.
  - Indictment No. 2 of George Jacobs Sr., for Afflicting Mercy Lewis (Returned Ignoramus), ecca1222
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 222.
  - Testimony of Abigail Williams v. George Jacobs Sr., ecca1223
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 223.
  - Examinations of George Jacobs Sr., ecca1224
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 224.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. George Jacobs Sr., ecca1225
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 225.
  - Statements of Sarah Bibber, Sarah Churchill, Elizabeth Hubbard, Mary Walcott & Mary Warren v. George Jacobs Sr., ecca1226
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 226.
  - Testimony of John DeRich v. George Jacobs Sr. et al., ecca1227
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 227.
  - Testimony of George Herrick v. George Jacobs Sr., ecca1228
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 228.
  - Deposition of Mercy Lewis v. George Jacobs Sr., ecca1229
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 229.
  - Deposition of Joseph Flint v. George Jacobs Sr., ecca1230
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 230.
  - Warrant No. 1 for the Apprehension of John Willard, ecca1231
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 231.
  - Indictment No. 3 of John Willard, for Afflicting Susannah Shelden (Returned Ignoramus), ecca1232
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 232.
  - Indictment No. 2 of John Willard, for Afflicting Ann Putnam Jr., ecca1233
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 233.
  - Indictment No. 1 of John Willard, for Afflicting Mercy Lewis, ecca1234
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 234.
  - Indictment No. 7 of John Willard, for Afflicting Elizabeth Hubbard, ecca1235
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 235.
  - Indictment No. 4 of John Willard, for Afflicting Abigail Williams, ecca1236
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 236.
  - Summons for Witnesses v. John Willard, ecca1237
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 237.
  - Warrant No. 2 for the Apprehension of John Willard, ecca1238
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 238.
  - Witnesses v. John Willard, ecca1239
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 239.
  - Testimony of Ann Putnam Sr. v. John Willard, William Hobbs & Martha Cory, ecca1240
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 240.
  - Testimony of Susannah Shelden v. Elizabeth Colson, George Jacobs Jr., Rebecca Jacobs, Elizabeth Procter, John Procter & John Willard, ecca1241
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 202 & 241.
  - Deposition of Samuel Parris, Nathaniel Ingersoll & Thomas Putnam v. John Willard, ecca1242
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 242.
  - Testimony of Susannah Shelden v. John Willard, ecca1243
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 243.
  - Statement of Susannah Shelden v. John Willard & Elizabeth Colson, ecca1244
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 244.
  - Testimony of Sarah Bibber v. John Willard, ecca1245
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 245.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Hubbard v. John Willard, ecca1246
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 246.
  - Deposition of Elizabeth Booth & Testimony of Susannah Shelden v. John Willard, ecca1247
    ECCA, Vol. 1, no. 247.